# Chuangqi Li

Macgregor, Brisbane 4109
+61 0405155518 | charlie.chuangqi.li@gmail.com
https://www.linkedin.com/in/chuangqi-li/
Personal Website: https://www.chuangqili.com

# **Career Objective**

Highly motivated Master of Information Technology with 3 years business experience in software development, currently seeking a new position in Front End web development. I am innovative and has strong problem-solving skills that can carry out projects effectively in teams to meet project requirements. My professional skills will bring continuous contribution and value to the role of web development.

#### **Technical Skills**

- Front End: HTML5, CSS3, Vue JS 2.x/3.x, React JS, uni-app, TypeScript, SASS, Flex, jQuery 3.x, JavaScript ES5/ES6/ES7/ ES8, Bootstrap 4, Element UI, Vant UI, Ant Design, iView UI
- Back End: Node.js, Express.js, Koa.js, GraphQL, Mongoose, Python
- GIS: Tencent Map API, Amap API, Google Map API, GeoJSON
- Data visualization: Apache ECharts, D3.js, Three.js
- Database: MYSQL, MongoDB
- Develop tools & Platforms: GitHub, GitLab, Bitbucket, Postman, Trello, SVN
- DevOps: Jenkins, Huawei cloud, Tencent cloud, Nginx, AWS, Docker
- Methodologies: Agile, Scrum, Kanban
- Architecture: RESTful APIs

## **Employment History**

VIZEN Tech Beijing, China

Front-end developer, Geographic Information Group

Nov 2021 – Jul 2022

# Digital Technology Park Network Application

- Based on the company's self-developed 3D panorama engine (VIZEN), use WebGL and Three.js to develop and optimize the 3D models of intelligent buildings.
- Upgraded the project to the latest version of Vue 3.0, compile and package it with webpack5, and deploy it on Huawei Cloud, which improves the project compilation speed, optimizes the development and production environment, and greatly improves the team's work efficiency.
- Successfully solved multiple interaction and data visualization problems of 3D model display and data display after architectural data analysis proposed by the project team.
- Commercial 3D engine URL: https://show.vizen.cn/

# Land Monitoring Mobile App

- Use Vue 3.0 and webpack5 to build the project, customize and encapsulate the Axios request, and realize the on-demand configuration of the project.
- Combine VANT UI library and flex layout to realize the adaptation of different screen sizes of Android and IOS.
- Use uni-app, the code of this project is refactored based on the WeChat platform.
- Use the API of Amap to realize the panoramas of Shunde City, Guangdong Province, China in different periods, the geographical location information of land and buildings in the panoramas, the drawing of map points and the visual display of geographical data.
- Use ECharts and 3D.js to draw more than 4,000 panoramic pictures collected into multiple dynamic charts at one time and analyze them in real time to realize data visualization and provide geographic data services for relevant institutions in Shunde City.
- Use Jenkins and AWS to maintain and manage the platform. Finally, the first version of uni-app was released on WeChat using WeChat developer tools, and the internal trial version of the company was successfully launched.

Front-end developer, Platform Architecture Group

## Medical data large screen

- Use ReactJS combined with Redux to develop large-screen applications.
- Use ECharts and Amap to dynamically display and update relevant medical data through asynchronous requests.
- Use the vw adaptation scheme and vue2.0 to adapt to large screens of different sizes to meet the needs of different hospitals.
- Utilize the AWS operation and maintenance project and successfully send it to the corresponding hospital for large-screen data display and analysis.

### "Five centres" medical system platform

- Use ReactJS combined with Redux to develop the pc side of the medical system web application.
- Use React Native to develop the tablet and mobile apps which is convenient for medical emergency use.
- Use JWT for login authority authentication and verification.
- Use ES6 Promises to implement asynchronous requests for large amounts of medical data.
- Use table components and ECharts to realize the development of all editable and static tables on the page to clearly display and analyze medical and patient data.

### ECG capture device (tablet with ECG device)

- Cooperating with the back-end, Android and hardware engineers, after the patient information is collected from the ECG device and transmitted to the system, the front-end calls the relevant API to display the collected ECG picture and the patient's information.
- Use the positioning API of Amap to call the API provided by Android developers to locate the position of the tablet in real time, so as to realize the real-time positioning of medical staff on the ambulance and the sharing and transmission of patient data.

JR Academy Brisbane, Australia Oct 2018 - Sep 2020

Front-end developer, internship

- Weather App: Skilled in using ReactJS, Redux, Bootstrap, Sass, Flexbox to achieve display weather condition almost every day in Brisbane.
- Personal Website: Using react to develop my personal website, the page is responsive through the combination of flex and grid, which can be applied to pc, tablet and mobile devices.
  - Use email.js to implement the function of sending email reminders to yourself after the form is submitted.
  - Using AWS S3 to store static data and packaged code.
  - Configuring DNS service through AWS route 53.
  - Finally speeding up the distribution of static and dynamic web content to users through Amazon CloudFront, the project was successfully deployed and launched.
  - Personal Website Url: https://www.chuangqili.com
- Commercial Project: Use Full stack technology, including ReactJS, Redux, Nodejs, RESTful API, GraphQL, Sass, Styled Components, CI/CD, MongoDB, AWS to develop several parts of JR Website, like program courses page and tutorials page.
  - Web Url: https://jiangren.com.au/

## **Education**

**Performance Education Professional Year** 

Brisbane, QLD Dec 2022 - present

Jan 2021 - Nov 2021